wedoitallvegas.com 2011-12-12

# We Do It All Vegas Privacy and Policies

**Privacy Policy**

1.    We Do It All Vegas, Inc collects non-public personal information about you when you register with Wedoitallvegas.com as an e-newsletter subscriber. This personal information may include your name and e-mail address. Credit card information is asked only when ordering materials.  Once received, this information is entered into a database that is the sole ownership of the We Do It All Vegas, Inc. 

2.    Security measures are implemented for the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders we have a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above. WeDoItAllVegas.com maintains it’s PCI Compliance.

3.    What is PCI? - The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) is a set of requirements designed to ensure that ALL companies that process, store or transmit credit card information maintain a secure environment.  Essentially any merchant that has a Merchant ID (MID).

4.    The WeDoItAllVegas.com uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, and to improve our services, while contacting you.  WeDoItAllVegas.com does not sell or share your personal information with other persons or companies.  This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not offline.

5.    Wedoitallvegas.com does contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our effectiveness. These providers are not permitted to use the information collected.

6.    Upon your permission we do provide information to our partners. Information will be sent only to those partners for whom you have given permission and that have contractually agreed to associations with We Do It All Vegas, Inc with a confidentiality agreement.

**Use of Cookies**

WeDoItAllVegas.com may use "Cookies" to enable the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize capture and remember certain information. Cookies may be used to store your inclinations based on the activity, enabling us to provide you with enhanced services such as shopping cart preferences.   You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can refuse cookies. You do this through your browser. You may do this by clicking on your browser’s HELP button and following the directions.

How can you **opt-out** , or remove your information you have provided to us. Modifying your e-mail subscription and choosing to opt-out of receiving WeDoItAllVegas.com e-mails is easy. Simply click on the **unsubscribe link** on the bottom of the newsletter page on wedoitallvegas.com where you will see an "To unsubscribe, click here." This will take you to a page where you will be removed from all future newsletter mailings. 

**Third Party Sites**

Wedoitallvegas.com may contain third party content or services from other websites and may be available to you from a link provided by We Do It All Vegas, Inc.  Any links or other websites not affiliated with We Do It All Vegas, Inc are not subject to this privacy policy. You should review the privacy policy at any third party's website to determine how that site protects your privacy. We Do It All Vegas, Inc is not responsible for the content of third party websites or actions of any third parties. We use third-party advertising companies when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices Wedoitallvegas.com is supplying you with the tools to limit information used by these companies, click here: (http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

**Legalities**

1.    Nothing in this site grants to you any license or right to use any Trademarks displayed on this site without the written permission of the owner of the Trademark. Your use or misuse of the Trademarks displayed on this site, or any other content on this site, is strictly prohibited.

2.    We Do It All Vegas discloses to law-enforcement and their agencies when required by law to do so. 

3.    We Do It All Vegas supplies to credit card companies in cases of customer fraud. 

4.    You agree to indemnify WeDoItAllVegas.com its officers, directors, employees, agents, members and affiliates against any and all third party claims, demands, liabilities, costs or expenses including any reasonable attorney’s fees, resulting from your breach of any of these terms and conditions.

**  
Feedback**

We welcome your comments and concerns about our privacy policy.  

**Contact Us** : [http://support.wedoitallvegas.com](http://support.wedoitallvegas.com/)/ or 702-243-2029

**Your Consent**

By using wedoitallvegas.com, you consent to our privacy policy.  
Thank you for visiting www.wedoitallvegas.com 

Corporate Mailing Address:

We Do It All Vegas, Inc.

P O Box 1168 

Naples, FL 34106
